{
    "subject": "Ilona_Szil\u00e1gyi",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Vlad_III_the_Impaler",
    "human_readable": "Ilona Szil\u00e1gyi is married to Vlad III the Impaler.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9167207479476929,
            "question": "Who is Ilona Szil\u00e1gyi married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8918827772140503,
            "question": "What is the connection between Ilona Szil\u00e1gyi and Vlad III the Impaler?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7757411599159241,
            "question": "Who was Ilona Szil\u00e1gyi?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6002300977706909,
            "question": "Where was Vlad III the Impaler from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5746763348579407,
            "question": "What is Vlad III the Impaler known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.47244879603385925,
            "question": "Is Vlad III the Impaler a historical figure?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.433260053396225,
            "question": "Are there any famous historical accounts about Vlad III the Impaler?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4301270544528961,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Vlad III the Impaler's reign?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4140395224094391,
            "question": "What is Ilona Szil\u00e1gyi's role in history?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.32196199893951416,
            "question": "What period in history did Vlad III the Impaler live in?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Ilona Szil\u00e1gyi is married to Vlad III the Impaler.",
            "html": "yago_26513_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Ilona Szil\u00e1gyi's role in history?",
            "html": "yago_26513_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about Vlad III the Impaler's reign?",
            "html": "yago_26513_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any famous historical accounts about Vlad III the Impaler?",
            "html": "yago_26513_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26513_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26513_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26513_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26513_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26513_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26513_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26513_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26513_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26513_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26513_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents consistently mention that Ilona Szil\u00e1gyi was married to Vlad III, who is also referred to as Vlad the Impaler."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}